

## CONTACTS

- - github.com/justkwer
- instagram.com/justkwer
- - Inkedin.com/in/kwer
- - t.me/justkwer
  - https://t.me/justkwer

### LANGUAGES

Russian (native)

English (intermediate)

#### SKILS

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React

TypeScript

Redux / RTK / Saga

React-query

Styled Components

Next.js

REST API

Git

Three.js

# ALEXI HANGULEV

Frontend Developer

# ABOUTME

Frontend developer with 4+ years experience. I usually write in React and Next, I also study Three.js (I have a lot of experience in 3D modeling).

am interested in information technologies and how they transform our lives.

There's nothing better than clean code and a working application.

## EXPERIENCE

- Frontend Developer at Freelance 2022-Present, Frontend
- Mogilev Energy
  2013-2022, Constructor

# EDUCATION

- Self-Education 2021-Present, Frontend
- The Rolling Scopes School 2021-2022, Frontend
- Belarusian-Russian University 2008-2013, Engineer